<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
        <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.10</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
        <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>Codewave</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
        <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware
            authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to
            http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad
        </MASTER_PAD_INFO>
    </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>Codewave Software Michael Descher</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>Saturnstr. 20</Address_1>
        <Address_2/>
        <City_Town>Rastatt</City_Town>
        <State_Province/>
        <Zip_Postal_Code>76437</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>Germany</Country>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.codewave.de</Company_WebSite_URL>
        <Contact_Info>
            <Author_First_Name>Michael</Author_First_Name>
            <Author_Last_Name>Descher</Author_Last_Name>
            <Author_Email>info@codewave.de</Author_Email>
            <Contact_First_Name>Michael</Contact_First_Name>
            <Contact_Last_Name>Descher</Contact_Last_Name>
            <Contact_Email>info@codewave.de</Contact_Email>
        </Contact_Info>
        <Support_Info>
            <Sales_Email>info@codewave.de</Sales_Email>
            <Support_Email>support@codewave.de</Support_Email>
            <General_Email>info@codewave.de</General_Email>
            <Sales_Phone/>
            <Support_Phone/>
            <General_Phone/>
            <Fax_Phone/>
        </Support_Info>
    </Company_Info>
    <Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>MyTunesRSS</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>3.8.0-RC-1</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>01</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>10</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2010</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars/>
        <Program_Cost_Other_Code>EUR</Program_Cost_Other_Code>
        <Program_Cost_Other>15</Program_Cost_Other>
        <Program_Type>Commercial</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>Beta</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>No Install Support</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Java,Win2000,Win7 x32,Win7 x64,WinVista,WinVista x64,WinXP</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English,German</Program_Language>
        <Program_Change_Info>
Configurable links to external sites for albums, artists and tracks, e.g. to link to Amazon.
Playlist editing with much improved usability.
Search can find exact matches like before or similar matches as well. Similar matches are standard. Improved performance when searching.
Much more comfortable user management.
Support for HTML in welcome message.
System tray support for Mac OS X added (known issues on Linux).
Windows bundle with installer (optionally can install Java runtime as well).
File cache for downloaded ZIP archives (support for download managers).
New function in web interface to set tags for tracks. You can also set tags for all tracks of an album, a playlist, etc.
All functions (rss feed, flash player, download, etc.) are available through a popup menu in the web interface now. So you can enable the ones you usually use in the settings like before and access the other ones through the menu if needed. So you can save display space by disabling some functions but also use them if needed.
When accessing the server with the iPhone the user is asked whether he wants to use the default interface or the iPhone optimized interface which does not have all functions of the default interface. The special iPhone service through http://iphone.mytunesrss.com will be disabled soon.
Optionally configure forced transcoders for a user, i.e. force transcoder usage for a user.
Simpler transcoder configuration for all media types (e.g. transcode AVI video to MP4 or FLV to play it in Flash player).
LDAP authentication support.
You can now configure multiple playlists if you want to restrict a user to a number of tracks.
Opensearch link in portal page. You can add the MyTunesRSS search to your Firefox (other browsers have not been tested yet) search plugins.
Bugfixes.
        </Program_Change_Info>
        <Program_Category_Class>Audio &amp; Multimedia::Other</Program_Category_Class>
        <Program_System_Requirements>Java 1.5</Program_System_Requirements>
        <File_Info>
            <File_Size_Bytes>36263644</File_Size_Bytes>
            <File_Size_K>0</File_Size_K>
            <File_Size_MB>0.0</File_Size_MB>
        </File_Info>
        <Expire_Info>
            <Has_Expire_Info>Y</Has_Expire_Info>
            <Expire_Count>30</Expire_Count>
            <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
            <Expire_Other_Info/>
            <Expire_Month/>
            <Expire_Day/>
            <Expire_Year/>
        </Expire_Info>
    </Program_Info>
    <Program_Descriptions>
        <English>
            <Keywords>audio video music streaming mp3 m4a mp4 mpeg rss m3u xspf itunes</Keywords>
            <Char_Desc_45>Access your music and video wherever you are.</Char_Desc_45>
            <Char_Desc_80>Access your music and video wherever you are. All you need is a web browser.</Char_Desc_80>
            <Char_Desc_250>Create RSS feeds, M3U or XSPF playlists, play MP3 music directly in your browser and much
                more. Create multiple user accounts, assign permissions, create download quotas and much more. Use your
                iTunes library or simple watch folders.
            </Char_Desc_250>
            <Char_Desc_450>Create RSS feeds, M3U or XSPF playlists, play MP3 music directly in your browser with a flash
                music player and much more. Create multiple user accounts, assign permissions, create download quotas
                and much more. Discover other MyTunesRSS servers on your local network. Use your iTunes library or
                simple watch folders. Upload new music to the server through the beautiful web interface. Browse your
                music library by album, artist or genre.
            </Char_Desc_450>
            <Char_Desc_2000>Create RSS feeds, M3U or XSPF playlists, play MP3 music directly in your browser with a
                flash music player and much more. Create multiple user accounts, assign permissions, create download
                quotas and much more. Discover other MyTunesRSS servers on your local network. Use your iTunes library
                or simple watch folders. Upload new music to the server through the beautiful web interface. Browse your
                music library by album, artist or genre. All the things you ever wanted to do!
            </Char_Desc_2000>
        </English>
    </Program_Descriptions>
    <Web_Info>
        <Application_URLs>
            <Application_Info_URL>http://www.codewave.de/products/mytunesrss</Application_Info_URL>
            <Application_Order_URL>http://www.codewave.de/products/mytunesrss/buy</Application_Order_URL>
            <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://codewave.dyn-o-saur.com/products/mytunesrss/server.png
            </Application_Screenshot_URL>
            <Application_Icon_URL>http://codewave.dyn-o-saur.com/products/mytunesrss/mytunesrss.gif
            </Application_Icon_URL>
            <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.codewave.de/products/mytunesrss/pad-win.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
        </Application_URLs>
        <Download_URLs>
            <Primary_Download_URL>http://www.codewave.de/products/mytunesrss/?download_file=mytunesrss-3.8.0-RC-1-setup.exe
            </Primary_Download_URL>
            <Secondary_Download_URL/>
            <Additional_Download_URL_1/>
            <Additional_Download_URL_2/>
        </Download_URLs>
    </Web_Info>
    <Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions/>
        <EULA/>
    </Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>